Contact

jasjeetbhullar94@gmail.com 9021062554 LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Sales Promotion · Financial
Analysis · Marketing · Research
· Market Research · Business
Development · Search Engine
Optimization (SEO) · Singing ·
Finance · Entrepreneurship

Accomplishments · See all

4 Certifications · 3 Languages

Recommendations · See all

Senthilkumaran NS
Business Manager at Redington
India Ltd

Shreejit Nandkumar Regional Manager-West Enterprise Sales (Mid market) at APC by Schneider Electric

Jasjeet Kaur

Deputy Manager(Marketing) - Microsoft Surface at Redington India Ltd

South Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

Experienced Group Sales Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Research, Market Research, Auditing, SPSS, and Sales Promotion and marketing. Strong sales professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Marketing & Finance from Lovely Professional University.

Experience

Deputy Manager(Marketing) - Microsoft Surface · Redington India

Ltd

July 2019 - Present · New Delhi

Responsible for Marketing activities and sales promotion for Microsoft surface PAN India.

Area Sales Manager · Redington India Ltd

August 2016 - Present · Pune Area, India

1.) Responsible for the Revenue growth for the Power Business while maintaining profitability at sales level2.) Developing and execution of Strategy in Marketing and Sales to target growth and increase the Market Share3.) Identifying and developing potential clients in the targeted markets ensuring maximum custom

Summer Intern · Verka

June 2015 - July 2015 (2 months) · Jalandhar Area, India

Education

Guru Nanak Dev University

Bachelor's Degree, B.com professional (2011 - 2014)